delightfoods.com 2017-03-22

# Privacy Policy

If you have indicated that you would like us to, we may also pass your information onto other companies in the GFOI retail group, or carefully selected third parties who may inform you about their products and services, which may be of interest to you.

If you are an existing patron, we will only contact you by electronic means (e-mail or SMS) with information about goods and services similar to those, which were the subject of a previous sale to you or something that might be of any interest to you as per our analysis pertaining to your behavior on our website.

If you are a new privileged patron, and where we permit selected third parties to use your data, we (or they) will contact you by electronic means only if you have consented to this.

If you do not want us to use your data in this way, or to pass your details on to third parties for marketing purposes, please tick the relevant box situated on the signup form on which we collect your data.

## How We Collect Your Information?

We may collect and process your information as follows:

  1. Information that you provide by filling in forms on our website for transactional, employment, services or any other purposes.
  2. Details of transactions you carry out through our site or when telephoning us and of the fulfillment of your orders.
  3. If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.
  4. When purchasing a gift or service for a third person. We may collect data pertaining to the addressee.
  5. We may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them.
  6. Details of your visits to our website and the resources that you access or view.
  7. Whilst posting messages on our message boards, chat rooms or other message areas or leaving feedback, we will collect that information. We preserve this information as necessary data to resolve disputes, provide customer support and troubleshoot problems as permitted by the Indian law.
  8. If our privileged patron connects with GFOI by emails, letters, whatsapp, customer service center or via any social networking website or if other users or third parties correspond to us about your activities or postings on the Website. We may also collect such information into a file specific to you.

## Disclosure of Your Information

We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries or any other entity concerning to GFOI.

We may disclose your personal information to third parties:

    1. In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal details to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.
    2. 2\. If we get in partnership with any other company or entity, in such an event we may disclose your personal information.
    3. 3\. If GFOI or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal details held by it about its patrons will be one of the transferred assets.
    4. 4\. If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal details in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of use or terms and

conditions of supply and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of GFOI, our customers or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

Keeping In Touch With GFOI for Your Rights

At GFOI we want to keep you up to date with information about new ranges, special offers and improvements to this site. If you decide you do not wish to be contacted by us, you can request that we stop using your information and that we stop mailing information to you, by writing to the Customer Services Department, quoting Security and Privacy Enquiry, at Customer Services, GFOI, 7/11, East end C main road, 39th Cross, 9th Block, Jayanagar, Bangalore-560069 or write to us at support@delightfoods.com.

If you no longer wish to receive emails from us, each email we send contains a simple, automated way for you to request that we stop. If you wish to do this, simply follow the instructions at the end of any email or please call our Customer Care Team who will be more than happy to help you. You may continue to receive mailings, which are already on route to you for a short period of time while your request is being processed.

Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal details to these websites.

We will not keep your personal information processed by us for any purpose or purposes for longer than is necessary for that purpose or for those purposes. The Data Protection Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Data Protection Act. Any access request may be subject to a small fee to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you. Security Policy

At GFOI we endeavor to keep the security of our website as the utmost priority. Our site uses software to provide high level SSL encryption technology. There are two simple ways to check if a page on our website is secure; firstly a small padlock sign will appear in the bottom bar of your browser and the 'http' will be replaced with 'https' in front of GFOI. Today in the browser address window. Although we use advanced security measures to protect your information against loss, misuse and alteration, as is the case with all computer networks linked to the internet, we cannot make absolute guarantees over the security of the information you provide over the internet and as such we cannot be held responsible for it whatsoever.

Please note that email correspondence is free format text and cannot be encrypted, therefore it is not at all a secure means of communication. We will never contact you by email to ask you to send or confirm any of your personal details; if we need any information of this nature we will only contact you by telephone.

Never send any sensitive information, such as passwords or credit card information, via email or SMS to anyone acting as us. Only an authorized GFOI customer care executive will get in-touch with under any such circumstances.

Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone – this refers to your personal account. Where We Store Your Information

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at our secured servers. It may also be processed by staff operating outside, who works for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff maybe engaged in, among other things, the fulfillment of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal details, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing.

GFOI take all steps reasonably essential to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Security and Privacy Policy.

## Changes to our security and privacy policy

Any changes we may make to our Security and Privacy Policy in the future will be posted on this page.

## Contact

Questions, comments and requests regarding this Security and Privacy are always welcomed and should be addressed to Customer Services Department, quoting Security and Privacy Enquiry, at Customer Services,   
GFOI, 7/11,   
East end C main road, 39th Cross,   
9th Block, Jayanagar,   
Bangalore-560069   
or   
write to us at - [support@delightfoods.com.](mailto:support@delightfoods.com.)
